sportdata.org 2010-06-07

# Privacy statement

Privacy statement  
---  
  
By entering and sending your data via the SET Online platform you agree that sportdata is allowed to collect, store and manipulate the individual-related data mentioned below. This agreement can be revoked any time. 

**§ 1  
Personal data**

sportdata collects, stores and uses personal data such as name, address, phone number, mail address and birth date only as far as it is necessary to provide its service as event management platform and for invoice. Personal data is only collected via electronic forms. 

**§ 2  
Usage data**

Usage data such as the beginning, ending and duration of usage are only collected, stored and used as far as this is necessary to provide sportdatas service as event management platform. 

**§ 3  
Compliancy**

The user agrees that sportdata uses individual-related data as far as this is necessary for the registration procedure and organisation of an event. In this meaning the user agrees that if there exist supervising organisations, such as federal sports federations, these organisations are also granted access to the entered data like the particular event manager.

**§ 4  
Prosecution and transmission of data**

In case of misuse of the SET Online platform sportdata is allowed to pass on the collected data to prosecution as well as to third persons who reasonably claim being harmed by a user via the SET Online platform. 

**§ 5  
Disclosure**

sportdata immediately informs any user about the storage status of his individual-related data free of charge. If demanded the information can also be given electronically.
